http://www.hasbean.co.uk/pages/privacy-policy

In My Mug this Christmas
Coronavirus (COVID-19)
Shipping
When does Hasbean roast?
In My Mug this Christmas
Coronavirus (COVID-19)
Shipping
When does Hasbean roast?
Packaging & Bag Recycling
Subscription FAQ
Privacy policy
At Has Bean Coffee Limited ("Hasbean") we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders and to provide a more personalised shopping experience. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy and feel free (in fact we encourage) you to get in touch and ask any questions - contact details are at the bottom.What information do we collect and how?When you place an order, we need to know your name, email address, delivery address, credit or debit card number and the card’s expiry date. This allows us to process and fulfil your orders and to notify you of the status of your order. We keep your details on file to make it more convenient for you to place additional orders in future. If you’d like us to remove your details and account entirely, please email remove@hasbean.co.uk and let us know.When you email us at orders@hasbean.co.uk, we collect your name and email address so we are able to respond to your query. We may additionally ask for your telephone number if a telephone conversation is necessary. This information is stored within our help desk software, Zendesk. If you would like your information removing please get in touch with us at remove@hasbean.co.ukWhen you enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address and email address so we can administer the contest and notify winners. We delete these details within 3 months of the contest ending.When you subscribe to our newsletter, we collect your email address to keep you up to date on all the latest products and happenings. If you wish to unsubscribe from this newsletter, please click the 'unsubscribe' link in any of the emails. If you aren’t sure if you’re subscribed but would like to unsubscribe, get in touch with us on remove@hasbean.co.ukWhen you take out an In My Mug coffee subscription, we need to know your name, email address, delivery address and payment details. This allows us to process and fulfil your orders and to notify you of the status of your order. We keep your details on file whilst you’re an active subscriber or if you've paused your subscription to make it more convenient for you to receive additional orders in future. We delete details about old subscribers 12 months after cancellation.If you’d like us to remove your details and account entirely, please email remove@hasbean.co.uk and let us know.
Cookies
A cookie is a small file that can be placed onto your device to help us identify and remember you. It's sent to your browser and saved locally on your computer, tablet or phone.
We use cookies so our website can identify you whilst you are shopping with us, administer the website and provide an overall improved experience for you, the shopper. Without cookies you wouldn't be able to do things like add products to your basket or progress to the checkout. Our cookies are not used to identify you personally. They contain non-identifiable information only, in most cases just a string of randomly generated numbers and letters.
Cookies are also used on our website to gather usage statistics for Google Analytics, we do this to help make sure the site is meeting the needs of its users and to help us make improvements, for example improving site search. We use Google Analytics to collect information about how people use this site - for example, what you click on, how long you spend on the site and how you got here. You can opt out of Google Analytics cookies if you would like to here.
The majority of current web browsing software accepts cookies automatically but you have the power to remove and disable them via the options in your browser. This action may impair your experience on our website and many others around the internet. For further information about managing cookies we recommend visiting the ICO website here.
How does Hasbean protect customer information?SSL encryption protects your experience at hasbean.co.uk and encrypts the information you enter during transmission.The shopping experience is provided by the Shopify platform, who take data, security and privacy very seriously. You can read more about the steps they have taken to comply with GDPR and information about their security levels here https://help.shopify.com/manual/your-account/GDPRWe never see your credit/debit card details directly ourselves. Payments are handled by PayPal or if you choose credit/debit card, Worldpay, a globally renowned payment processor. Read more about Worldpay security here https://www.worldpay.com/uk/support/safeguard-your-businessWe comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 and EU General Data Protection Regulations and PEC regulations https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-pecr/what-are-pecrWill Hasbean disclose the information it collects to third parties?Any information we collect about you is exclusively used by Hasbean and nobody else. Hasbean does not sell, trade or rent your personal information to anybody. How long will Hasbean use your personal data for? We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. If you’d like us to remove your details and account entirely, please email remove@hasbean.co.uk and let us know. Privacy Policy AmendmentsWe reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website.Any questions?We respect your privacy and value your custom - if you have any questions and comments concerning privacy or the information we hold about you, please email us: privacy@hasbean.co.uk
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
